<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>foss on A Nerd&#39;s Tale</title>
    <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/tags/foss/</link>
    <description>Recent content in foss on A Nerd&#39;s Tale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2019 - Kuntal Majumder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 22:16:35 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hellozee.dev/tags/foss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #11 | Bi weekly from now</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 22:16:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw11/</guid>
      <description>It has been some tough few months and this would probably linger for a bit more. Nothing much serious but then my calendar is facing some trouble to sew some recreational hours into the schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #10</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 02:42:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw10/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, you don&#39;t want to know the number of bugs in our bug tracker at this point. But I assure you these are just our broken unit tests rather than bugs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #9</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 21:38:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw9/</guid>
      <description>With everyone getting back into work, we have managed to control the number of bugs. There are 2 fewer bugs than what I reported last time. I know it is still not a lot, but with Dmitry not available for most of the time and team having to divide its time between the resource rewrite &amp;amp; bug fixing, it is pretty good that the number is decreasing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #8</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 22:15:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw8/</guid>
      <description>The number of bugs has risen to 457 as it was a vacation season. Also, Dmitry is on parental leave, so the increase is quite normal.
As Boud is back from vacation, he is sharing his time between, bug fixing &amp;amp; triaging and administration stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #7</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 18:00:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw7/</guid>
      <description>My exams are over and hopefully I would back in for doing weeklies again, unless there is an Internet Shutdown in my area. Anyway, looking at the bug count we have 440 bugs open, 11 more bugs than what I reported in the last weekly (which was 12 days back).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #6</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 22:09:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw6/</guid>
      <description>We had a release last week and boy, I would just skip talking about bugs for this one. But we currently have 429 open bugs, 14 more from what I reported last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #5</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 09:11:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw5/</guid>
      <description>This week we got 13 new bug reports while 22 got fixed, a net decrease of 9 bugs. The bug tracker says that there are about 415 bugs remaining, so still a long way to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #4</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 21:22:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw4/</guid>
      <description>Phew, I am late this week for the update, kudos to my university exams nevertheless better be late than never. One more week passed, we are now closing on the 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tons of Bug Fixes | Krita Weekly #3</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 18:33:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw3/</guid>
      <description>The number of bug reports have rose from 18 to 33 this week, out if which my magnetic lasso is guilty of a couple. I promise I will take care of them as soon as I get rid of the university exams which are coming up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JPEG 2K, Auto Precision | Krita Weekly #2</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 13:46:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw2/</guid>
      <description>This week in Krita has been more around features, rather than bug fixing. We had around 18 bug reports but at the same time 18 bugs were fixed too.
We can now import jpeg2000 files into Krita.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #1</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 17:58:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw1/</guid>
      <description>Preface Okay, so recently one of Boud&#39;s posts sparked some conversations in hackernews and reddit. So this is my part of taking care of a couple of the points raised in those discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is the year of Linux Desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/linux-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 19:46:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/linux-desktop/</guid>
      <description>The title is a running joke now, please don&#39;t hit me, I know that this is one hell of an aloof conclusion. But why? Let&#39;s retrospect the situation.
 Linux is just the kernel Add a display server on top of it Add a window manager Add a compositor Add a display manager  You will get a desktop, yes a desktop and not a desktop environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>