<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Nerd&#39;s Tale</title>
    <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Nerd&#39;s Tale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2019 - Kuntal Majumder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 16:23:10 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hellozee.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #14 | GSoC is on</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 16:23:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw14/</guid>
      <description>After an anxious month, I am writing a Krita Weekly again and probably this would be my last one too, though I hope not. Let&amp;rsquo;s start by talking about bugs. Unlike the trend going about the last couple of months, the numbers have taken a serious dip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commentary on the Qt situation</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/thoughts-on-qt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 19:37:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/thoughts-on-qt/</guid>
      <description>A lot of things have been going on with Qt these days. It all started with The Qt Company trying to get an increase in their revenues, specifically this blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weeky #13 | 4.2.9 released</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 16:11:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw13/</guid>
      <description>So one of the toughest Krita releases is up today. Tough not in the sense there were a lot of regressions to solve but the mountain of build issues faced by the team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenType, Harfbuzz, Qt : Not exactly a love story</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/freetype-harfbuzz-fonts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 15:31:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/freetype-harfbuzz-fonts/</guid>
      <description>Was experimenting with rendering text in Qt, of course for trying to see if I can land some improvements over Krita&amp;rsquo;s existing text tool. And now that as I have played with it a bit, jotting some notes over this blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #12 | 4.2.9 beta released</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 17:16:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw12/</guid>
      <description>So, a lot has been going around these days, 2020 hasn&amp;rsquo;t been the best year so far. Nevertheless don&amp;rsquo;t panic, maintain proper hygiene and you should be fine for the most part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #11 | Bi weekly from now</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 22:16:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw11/</guid>
      <description>It has been some tough few months and this would probably linger for a bit more. Nothing much serious but then my calendar is facing some trouble to sew some recreational hours into the schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A year as a KDE developer | The KUnity Setup</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/a_year_as_a_kde_developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 17:25:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/a_year_as_a_kde_developer/</guid>
      <description>It has been more than a year that I had push rights for all the KDE repositories. So this is an obligatory anniversary post.
I got introduced to Linux while searching for development environments that came with all sorts of compilers &amp;amp; interpreters by default and I don&amp;rsquo;t have to manually install those stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #10</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 02:42:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw10/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, you don&amp;rsquo;t want to know the number of bugs in our bug tracker at this point. But I assure you these are just our broken unit tests rather than bugs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #9</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 21:38:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw9/</guid>
      <description>With everyone getting back into work, we have managed to control the number of bugs. There are 2 fewer bugs than what I reported last time. I know it is still not a lot, but with Dmitry not available for most of the time and team having to divide its time between the resource rewrite &amp;amp; bug fixing, it is pretty good that the number is decreasing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #8</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 22:15:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw8/</guid>
      <description>The number of bugs has risen to 457 as it was a vacation season. Also, Dmitry is on parental leave, so the increase is quite normal.
As Boud is back from vacation, he is sharing his time between, bug fixing &amp;amp; triaging and administration stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux doesnt have Photoshop</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/linux_doesnt_have_photoshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 21:12:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/linux_doesnt_have_photoshop/</guid>
      <description>Linux doesn&amp;rsquo;t have Photoshop.
 One common rant I get to hear when I try to help someone to switch to Linux. It is almost 2020 and say what? people still agree with this statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C&#43;&#43; Rookie tries C#</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/cpp_rookie_on_csharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/cpp_rookie_on_csharp/</guid>
      <description>A little bit background, I am a final year undergrad student, looking for a job, which of course who isn&amp;rsquo;t these days. With that being said, my job search isn&amp;rsquo;t going quite well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #7</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 18:00:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw7/</guid>
      <description>My exams are over and hopefully I would back in for doing weeklies again, unless there is an Internet Shutdown in my area. Anyway, looking at the bug count we have 440 bugs open, 11 more bugs than what I reported in the last weekly (which was 12 days back).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #6</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 22:09:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw6/</guid>
      <description>We had a release last week and boy, I would just skip talking about bugs for this one. But we currently have 429 open bugs, 14 more from what I reported last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #5</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 09:11:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw5/</guid>
      <description>This week we got 13 new bug reports while 22 got fixed, a net decrease of 9 bugs. The bug tracker says that there are about 415 bugs remaining, so still a long way to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #4</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 21:22:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw4/</guid>
      <description>Phew, I am late this week for the update, kudos to my university exams nevertheless better be late than never. One more week passed, we are now closing on the 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tons of Bug Fixes | Krita Weekly #3</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 18:33:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw3/</guid>
      <description>The number of bug reports have rose from 18 to 33 this week, out if which my magnetic lasso is guilty of a couple. I promise I will take care of them as soon as I get rid of the university exams which are coming up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JPEG 2K, Auto Precision | Krita Weekly #2</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 13:46:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw2/</guid>
      <description>This week in Krita has been more around features, rather than bug fixing. We had around 18 bug reports but at the same time 18 bugs were fixed too.
We can now import jpeg2000 files into Krita.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Weekly #1</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 17:58:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/kw1/</guid>
      <description>Preface Okay, so recently one of Boud&amp;rsquo;s posts sparked some conversations in hackernews and reddit. So this is my part of taking care of a couple of the points raised in those discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One hell of a October</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/hell_of_october/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 20:32:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/hell_of_october/</guid>
      <description>October has been really great for me this year. It started with the Ada Lovelace Day meetup, or better, the after meetup party. The following week, my 6 months of effort got merged to master.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Am a Pilgrim</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/pycon_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:55:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/pycon_2019/</guid>
      <description>A pilgrimage is a journey, often into an unknown or foreign place, where a person goes in search of new or expanded meaning about the self, others, nature, or a higher good, through the experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To be Merged in master</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/to_be_merged_in_master/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 22:14:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/to_be_merged_in_master/</guid>
      <description>So, finally it seems like, after crossing the deadline by a couple months, Magnetic Lasso is going to get merged, as Boud told me. Lets see how many more weeks it takes, so presumably it is complete feature wise but who knows from where a bug might pop up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October Begins</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/october_begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 02:38:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/october_begins/</guid>
      <description>So my mid semester break begins next week, finally I can take sometime off my academics and get some shit done.
To start off the weekend, I started working on the Magnetic Lasso again, it is almost complete, there are still some UX issues remaining, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think it won&amp;rsquo;t take much time, considering that most of the work is done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Week with Conan</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/a_week_with_conan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 20:00:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/a_week_with_conan/</guid>
      <description>If someone has been following my posts, they would sure know, I write C++ for most of the time, I spent to write any piece of code. The reaction to which most people resonate is, &amp;ldquo;ouch, you write c++, that must be really tough&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not that much of an eventful week</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/eventful_week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/eventful_week/</guid>
      <description>To be fair, my speaking skills probably haven&amp;rsquo;t improved that much, but I no longer feel nervous while on the stage, like I used to feel earlier, thanks to the session that I took on the recent ILUGD meetup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck typing</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/duck_typing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 15:20:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/duck_typing/</guid>
      <description>Definition: Duck typing in computer programming is an application of the duck test—&amp;ldquo;If it walks like a duck and it quacks like a duck, then it must be a duck&amp;rdquo;—to determine if an object can be used for a particular purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Edge</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/finding_the_edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 17:12:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/finding_the_edge/</guid>
      <description>Three months of fighting with boost, qt, having a proper plan, multiple individuals to get help from and still unable to hit the target in time. That will be software engineering 101 for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magnetic Lasso for Krita is here</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/magnetic_lasso_is_here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 16:27:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/magnetic_lasso_is_here/</guid>
      <description>Update: This feature is now merged into master and can be tested out by downloading any of the Krita Next version. The UX has changed a lot, here is an updated post about the UX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Sprint 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/krita_sprint_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:18:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/krita_sprint_2019/</guid>
      <description>The sprint has officially ended yesterday and most of the participants have already left, except me, Ivan, Wolthera and Jouni. Well I would have also left as planned but I read my flight timings wrong and it would leave after 3 hours of what I thought the departure time was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The CircuitPython Act</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/the_circuitpython_act/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 19:47:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/the_circuitpython_act/</guid>
      <description>This would be pretty big post, might take up a day or two more than a week to complete, so please bear with me.
Context I had a flight for Amsterdam to catch, was a long flight, writing a post seems to be the best time killer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint ahoy</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/sprint_is_here/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 20:58:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/sprint_is_here/</guid>
      <description>Well, I did manage to get some work done during the start of the week cause after that it was just dripping nose and back to back headaches along with a sore throat for around the next 3 days, and I also had to prepare for Krita sprints happening next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Somewhat Usable</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/somewhat_usable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 11:42:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/somewhat_usable/</guid>
      <description>Adding a feature by yourself is a lot satisfying than requesting someone to add that for you, cause now you are both the producer and the consumer. But to be honest, I never thought I would be the one implementing the Magnetic Lasso for Krita when I requested it 4 years back, leave the fact that I even getting paid for doing so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A few more steps</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/a_few_more_steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 09:01:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/a_few_more_steps/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, working on correcting the checkpoint procedure made the tool explode. So I decided to take a couple of steps back and rethink the strategy. And for inspiration, I fired up YouTube and started watching tutorials of Photoshop&amp;rsquo;s Magnetic Lasso, cause that was the one which made me write this thing in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is coming alive</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/it_coming_alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 06:25:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/it_coming_alive/</guid>
      <description>After digging for around a month and a half, I can finally do some selections with the Magnetic Lasso tool, which I wrote with utter laziness as I would say. Though it still demands a lot of work to be done, so it will be just polishing the existing code into perfection for the next one and half month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topsy-turvy 5th Week</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/topsy_turvy_5th_week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 19:32:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/topsy_turvy_5th_week/</guid>
      <description>Finally, I can write myself as a professional developer, cause for the first time I got paid, that also by cash, for writing code. So after the boost battle of last month, it was time to test the algorithm out in the wild and not limit it to the confined boundary of the tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deliverable 1 : [✓]</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/deliverable_one_checked/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:48:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/deliverable_one_checked/</guid>
      <description>Finally done with the first phase of the feature I wanted, 4 years back. Though just the unit test for the algorithm is implemented. At least for now, we can detect edges and stick to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Done with boost</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/done_with_boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 00:16:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/done_with_boost/</guid>
      <description>This would start with a quote:
 Documentation is like sex: when it is good, it is very, very good; and when it is bad, it is better than nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Week with boost::graph</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/another_week_with_boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 13:29:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/another_week_with_boost/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;prelude&amp;gt;
In the previous post, I discussed boost::astar_search and ignored the most important part of the whole setup, the graph itself. This I would say is a little harder to comprehend than boost::astar_search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting boost::astar_search</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/boost_astar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 04:43:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/boost_astar/</guid>
      <description>Right now, I am having a hard time understanding BGL&amp;rsquo;s (the Boost Graph Library) template spaghetti, so decided to write a blogpost while I decipher it, one at a time, documenting the whole thing along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is the year of Linux Desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/linux-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 19:46:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/linux-desktop/</guid>
      <description>The title is a running joke now, please don&amp;rsquo;t hit me, I know that this is one hell of an aloof conclusion. But why? Let&amp;rsquo;s retrospect the situation.
 Linux is just the kernel Add a display server on top of it Add a window manager Add a compositor Add a display manager  You will get a desktop, yes a desktop and not a desktop environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/summer-is-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 14:18:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/summer-is-coming/</guid>
      <description>Note: Not a Game of Thrones fan, yet to watch even a single episode, but I wanted a catchy title
 This will be a story, so get prepared to be bored, 😸.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows : A true nightmare</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:31:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/windows/</guid>
      <description>I never expected such a dreadful day would come such that I have to install Windows, cause I didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough money. And yes, you read it right, nothing is wrong in the previous statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Design Works?</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/how-design-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 03:41:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/how-design-works/</guid>
      <description>Note: The title may be misleading, 😛
 I started dabbling with graphic design back when I was in 7th grade, that time I saw someone working in Photoshop, probably was extracting a person and putting that extracted piece on top another picture, the wow moment that was and I be like I also want to do that, so got a copy of Adobe Photoshop 7, technically a pirated copy but well, Photoshop 7 was not being sold anymore back then and I was just experimenting with it, so ethically I was like, okay, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t hurt anyone, let that be so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caring about the directories</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/dexer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 20:05:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/dexer/</guid>
      <description>The story begins in PyCon India 2018, I, with a tired soul (registration desk is not a quite nice place for resting), shivering in freezing cold, after a dosage of Paracetamol, asked fhackdroid to tell me about any project which uses Go, so that I can also put some patches during devsprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is New Year my dudes</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/new-year-bois/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 23:31:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/new-year-bois/</guid>
      <description>If you don&amp;rsquo;t get the meme reference from the title, here is one more for you :
 Enough of memes, lets talk about something trendy, something that everyone is talking about cause January 2019 is all about setting up goals and resolutions, I am not being punny here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flashback 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/flashback-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 16:49:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/flashback-2018/</guid>
      <description>tl;dr, Typical end of the year post as you may expect.
Well, 2018 was a significantly productive year for me compared to other years, learned so many things which I wanted to, plus added more things to the bucket list for the coming year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recreating the Marvel Intro with Python and Nuke</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/nuke-python-marvel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 15:07:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/nuke-python-marvel/</guid>
      <description>Let me start this one with a story.
Once there was a kid who loved to play games, after a while, he wanted to make games of his own and tada a programmer was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another year, nice one</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/ilugd-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 12:58:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/ilugd-birthday/</guid>
      <description>So apparently one of the oldest community in probably the whole India, celebrated its 2nd anniversary on 28th after it was revived back on 2016. And you know what, this time it was a Capture The Flag event, something new tried by the new group of people who joined hands to not let this community go in hibernation again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Year Passes by</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/ilugd-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 21:43:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/ilugd-year/</guid>
      <description>ILUGD better known as India Linux Users Group - Delhi, a LUG, based in Delhi NCR. Bear in mind that it is &amp;ldquo;India&amp;rdquo; and not &amp;ldquo;Indian&amp;rdquo;, a lot of people get that incorrect, &amp;ldquo;Indian&amp;rdquo; means it is exclusively for Indians which we are obviously not, but our group is based in Delhi which comes in India so, hashtag_blah_blah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Languages are just tools, you idiot</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 19:27:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/languages/</guid>
      <description>Note: Don&amp;rsquo;t take the title onto your ego
 For sake of clarity, I would like to make some terms used in the post clear, it may mean something other to you but for the simplicity of the post, I would be using them in a particular way:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do it, you may learn something new</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/cook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 22:04:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/cook/</guid>
      <description>Frankly speaking Computer Graphics is a subject which is not appreciated by most of students who study Computer Science just like Real Analysis in Mathematics but being a nerd, this were the perfect subjects which could act like stimulant for my neurons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>