<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Nerd&#39;s Tale</title>
    <link>http://www.hellozee.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Nerd&#39;s Tale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2018 - Kuntal Majumder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 22:11:39 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.hellozee.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.hellozee.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 22:11:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hellozee.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Kuntal, sophomore at Delhi University, will be majoring in Computer Science, love working with statically typed languages, currently taking my time to understand how light bounces off the surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another year, nice one</title>
      <link>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/ilugd-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 12:58:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/ilugd-birthday/</guid>
      <description>So apparently one of the oldest community in probably the whole India, celebrated its 2nd anniversary on 28th after it was revived back on 2016. And you know what, this time it was a Capture The Flag event, something new tried by the new group of people who joined hands to not let this community go in hibernation again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Year Passes by</title>
      <link>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/ilugd-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 21:43:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/ilugd-year/</guid>
      <description>ILUGD better known as India Linux Users Group - Delhi, a LUG, based in Delhi NCR. Bear in mind that it is &amp;ldquo;India&amp;rdquo; and not &amp;ldquo;Indian&amp;rdquo;, a lot of people get that incorrect, &amp;ldquo;Indian&amp;rdquo; means it is exclusively for Indians which we are obviously not, but our group is based in Delhi which comes in India so, hashtag_blah_blah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Languages are just tools, you idiot</title>
      <link>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 19:27:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/languages/</guid>
      <description>Note: Don&amp;rsquo;t take the title onto your ego
 For sake of clarity, I would like to make some terms used in the post clear, it may mean something other to you but for the simplicity of the post, I would be using them in a particular way:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something to be scared of..</title>
      <link>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/something_to_be_scared_of/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 12:47:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/something_to_be_scared_of/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article is purposefully written in order to offend people, the author just wanted to clear his mind. And as you can see the category says self satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do it, you may learn something new</title>
      <link>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/cook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 22:04:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/cook/</guid>
      <description>Frankly speaking Computer Graphics is a subject which is not appreciated by most of students who study Computer Science just like Real Analysis in Mathematics but being a nerd, this were the perfect subjects which could act like stimulant for my neurons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>