<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pycon on A Nerd&#39;s Tale</title>
    <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/tags/pycon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pycon on A Nerd&#39;s Tale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2019 - Kuntal Majumder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 20:32:56 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hellozee.dev/tags/pycon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>One hell of a October</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/hell_of_october/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 20:32:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/hell_of_october/</guid>
      <description>October has been really great for me this year. It started with the Ada Lovelace Day meetup, or better, the after meetup party. The following week, my 6 months of effort got merged to master.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Am a Pilgrim</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/pycon_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:55:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/pycon_2019/</guid>
      <description>A pilgrimage is a journey, often into an unknown or foreign place, where a person goes in search of new or expanded meaning about the self, others, nature, or a higher good, through the experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October Begins</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/october_begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 02:38:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/october_begins/</guid>
      <description>So my mid semester break begins next week, finally I can take sometime off my academics and get some shit done.
To start off the weekend, I started working on the Magnetic Lasso again, it is almost complete, there are still some UX issues remaining, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think it won&amp;rsquo;t take much time, considering that most of the work is done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caring about the directories</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/dexer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 20:05:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/dexer/</guid>
      <description>The story begins in PyCon India 2018, I, with a tired soul (registration desk is not a quite nice place for resting), shivering in freezing cold, after a dosage of Paracetamol, asked fhackdroid to tell me about any project which uses Go, so that I can also put some patches during devsprint.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>