<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kde on A Nerd&#39;s Tale</title>
    <link>http://www.hellozee.me/tags/kde/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kde on A Nerd&#39;s Tale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2018 - Kuntal Majumder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 19:46:48 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.hellozee.me/tags/kde/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This is the year of Linux Desktop</title>
      <link>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/linux-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 19:46:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/linux-desktop/</guid>
      <description>The title is a running joke now, please don&amp;rsquo;t hit me, I know that this is one hell of an aloof conclusion. But why? Let&amp;rsquo;s retrospect the situation.
 Linux is just the kernel Add a display server on top of it Add a window manager Add a compositor Add a display manager  You will get a desktop, yes a desktop and not a desktop environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is coming...</title>
      <link>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/summer-is-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 14:18:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/summer-is-coming/</guid>
      <description>Note: Not a Game of Thrones fan, yet to watch even a single episode, but I wanted a catchy title
 This will be a story, so get prepared to be bored, 😸.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Design Works?</title>
      <link>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/how-design-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 03:41:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hellozee.me/posts/how-design-works/</guid>
      <description>Note: The title may be misleading, 😛
 I started dabbling with graphic design back when I was in 7th grade, that time I saw someone working in Photoshop, probably was extracting a person and putting that extracted piece on top another picture, the wow moment that was and I be like I also want to do that, so got a copy of Adobe Photoshop 7, technically a pirated copy but well, Photoshop 7 was not being sold anymore back then and I was just experimenting with it, so ethically I was like, okay, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t hurt anyone, let that be so.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>