<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>open-source on A Nerd&#39;s Tale</title>
    <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/tags/open-source/</link>
    <description>Recent content in open-source on A Nerd&#39;s Tale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2019 - Kuntal Majumder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 16:27:27 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hellozee.dev/tags/open-source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Magnetic Lasso for Krita is here</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/magnetic_lasso_is_here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 16:27:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/magnetic_lasso_is_here/</guid>
      <description>I won&amp;rsquo;t say that I am done with Magnetic Lasso now, but the results are a lot better now to be honest. Take a look at one of the tests that I did,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krita Sprint 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/krita_sprint_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:18:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/krita_sprint_2019/</guid>
      <description>The sprint has officially ended yesterday and most of the participants have already left, except me, Ivan, Wolthera and Jouni. Well I would have also left as planned but I read my flight timings wrong and it would leave after 3 hours of what I thought the departure time was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint ahoy</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/sprint_is_here/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 20:58:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/sprint_is_here/</guid>
      <description>Well, I did manage to get some work done during the start of the week cause after that it was just dripping nose and back to back headaches along with a sore throat for around the next 3 days, and I also had to prepare for Krita sprints happening next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Somewhat Usable</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/somewhat_usable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 11:42:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/somewhat_usable/</guid>
      <description>Adding a feature by yourself is a lot satisfying than requesting someone to add that for you, cause now you are both the producer and the consumer. But to be honest, I never thought I would be the one implementing the Magnetic Lasso for Krita when I requested it 4 years back, leave the fact that I even getting paid for doing so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A few more steps</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/a_few_more_steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 09:01:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/a_few_more_steps/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, working on correcting the checkpoint procedure made the tool explode. So I decided to take a couple of steps back and rethink the strategy. And for inspiration, I fired up YouTube and started watching tutorials of Photoshop&amp;rsquo;s Magnetic Lasso, cause that was the one which made me write this thing in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is coming alive</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/it_coming_alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 06:25:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/it_coming_alive/</guid>
      <description>After digging for around a month and a half, I can finally do some selections with the Magnetic Lasso tool, which I wrote with utter laziness as I would say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topsy-turvy 5th Week</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/topsy_turvy_5th_week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 19:32:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/topsy_turvy_5th_week/</guid>
      <description>Finally, I can write myself as a professional developer, cause for the first time I got paid, that also by cash, for writing code. So after the boost battle of last month, it was time to test the algorithm out in the wild and not limit it to the confined boundary of the tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deliverable 1 : [✓]</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/deliverable_one_checked/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:48:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/deliverable_one_checked/</guid>
      <description>Finally done with the first phase of the feature I wanted, 4 years back. Though just the unit test for the algorithm is implemented. At least for now, we can detect edges and stick to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Done with boost</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/done_with_boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 00:16:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/done_with_boost/</guid>
      <description>This would start with a quote:
 Documentation is like sex: when it is good, it is very, very good; and when it is bad, it is better than nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Week with boost::graph</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/another_week_with_boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 13:29:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/another_week_with_boost/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;prelude&amp;gt;
In the previous post, I discussed boost::astar_search and ignored the most important part of the whole setup, the graph itself. This I would say is a little harder to comprehend than boost::astar_search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting boost::astar_search</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/boost_astar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 04:43:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/boost_astar/</guid>
      <description>Right now, I am having a hard time understanding BGL&amp;rsquo;s (the Boost Graph Library) template spaghetti, so decided to write a blogpost while I decipher it, one at a time, documenting the whole thing along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/summer-is-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 14:18:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/summer-is-coming/</guid>
      <description>Note: Not a Game of Thrones fan, yet to watch even a single episode, but I wanted a catchy title
 This will be a story, so get prepared to be bored, 😸.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Alight</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/getting-alight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 01:01:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/getting-alight/</guid>
      <description>Would start this one with a quote,
 Information is free - You have to know
People are not - You have to pay
Contributors are priceless - You have to be</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows : A true nightmare</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:31:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/windows/</guid>
      <description>I never expected such a dreadful day would come such that I have to install Windows, cause I didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough money. And yes, you read it right, nothing is wrong in the previous statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caring about the directories</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/dexer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 20:05:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/dexer/</guid>
      <description>The story begins in PyCon India 2018, I, with a tired soul (registration desk is not a quite nice place for resting), shivering in freezing cold, after a dosage of Paracetamol, asked fhackdroid to tell me about any project which uses Go, so that I can also put some patches during devsprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another year, nice one</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/ilugd-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 12:58:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/ilugd-birthday/</guid>
      <description>So apparently one of the oldest community in probably the whole India, celebrated its 2nd anniversary on 28th after it was revived back on 2016. And you know what, this time it was a Capture The Flag event, something new tried by the new group of people who joined hands to not let this community go in hibernation again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Year Passes by</title>
      <link>https://www.hellozee.dev/ilugd-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 21:43:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hellozee.dev/ilugd-year/</guid>
      <description>ILUGD better known as India Linux Users Group - Delhi, a LUG, based in Delhi NCR. Bear in mind that it is &amp;ldquo;India&amp;rdquo; and not &amp;ldquo;Indian&amp;rdquo;, a lot of people get that incorrect, &amp;ldquo;Indian&amp;rdquo; means it is exclusively for Indians which we are obviously not, but our group is based in Delhi which comes in India so, hashtag_blah_blah.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>